When you make a uniform skirt, you will usually encounter problems such as uneven folding and irregularity.
As shown in the video, there will be irregularities after the skirt is made.
The reason for these problems is that the skirt is folded while imitating the sewing line.
Let's do an example.
You may arrange the skirt pattern at the point of arrangement around the skirt, and then sew up these patterns.
After this operation, there will be irregularity after the skirt is opened.
This is because there is an irregularity after the skirt is opened.
When making a skirt, the skirt itself has a sewing line, and the skirt does not have the folding angle yet.
The skirt cannot be folded well under the function of the sewing line.
The solution to this problem is very simple, which is to fold the skirt first.
Here we have added the sewing line, so we need to temporarily anti-activate these sewing lines.
Click and drag the mouse button at the 2D window to select all the sewing lines here in the skirt and anti-activate.
Then in the 3D window, it is best not to have an intersection between the panels, otherwise it may not be stable.
The hard-painted panel can apply a very hard fabric to the panel, and the fold is also easier to appear.
The sewing line between the panels also needs to be anti-activated, and then you can start to simulate.
At this time, the panel will be folded.
In order to prevent the panel from falling to the ground, you can pull it higher and simulate it again.
If the panel is folded more accurately, then activate the sewing line.
After folding, activate the sewing line.
Pay attention to check if there is any part of the waist belt that has not been anti-activated.
After all is activated, you can start to simulate.
The sewing line will work again.
Please activate the side sewing line at the end.
Sometimes the panel is relatively large, and it may be more or less, and it will be interspersed.
If the side sewing line is activated, there may be an unstable problem.
Then solve the hardening, let the panel fall naturally, and then activate the side sewing line.
Then it is sort of finished.
Please look forward to the next time.
Thank you for your attention.
Please subscribe to this channel.
When you see the next video, please press the like button, and the bell will be activated.
See you next time.
Bye-bye.